

CONTACT ME

+216 25 960 738

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/wissem-zeddini-3829b4179/

PROFILE

I'm a Developer & Devops, Versatile, open-minded, sociable, dynamic, organized and motivated, I master the various tools of DevOps, development and the technologies necessary for a Data scientist. Also, I m expert in python development.

LANGUAGES

- Arabe (native language)
- English (good)
- Français (intermediate)

HOBBIES

- Football
- Movies
- Video Games

Wissem Zeddini

Devops & Developer

SKILLS

Programing/Scripting: Python, C, JavaScript, PHP, C#, Shell, PowerShell

WEB: PHP, Flask, Django, Symfony, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React, Fastify, Node is

DataBase: Mysql, SQL Server, Postgresql

API: Restful, GraphQL

Devops: Github Action, Gitlab CI, Jenkins, Terraform, Ansible,

Docker, Azure Devops

Cloud: Azure, AWS

Data Analysis & AI: Power BI, Pandas, Scikit learn, Open CV

Microsoft: Office 365, Copilot Studio, Power Automate, Power

Apps, Dataverse, Power Page

ERP: Dynamics

EXPÉRIENCES PROFESSIONNELLES

Developer & Devops

Rimans Solution - Amdoun, Beja | 2023 - 2023

- Mange CI/CD Piepline: Create and update jenkins pipelines.
- Create IaC pipelines: Create Infrastructure as a code pipelines using terraform to deploy resources on aws, and azure.
- Developer on Microsoft Power Platform: Create solutions using power automate, power apps, copilot, studios & omnichannel for customer service.

QA Tester & Automation

OPAL-RT - Canada | 2023

- Mange Jenkins Pipelines.
- Create automated tests using python, pytest.
- Debud Fail tests.
- Board Follow up.

Devops & Data Analysis

ZMWARE – Beja, Tunis | 2021 - 2022

- Data analysis on shopify stores: Data extraction and, data reporting and data visualisations.
- Devops: Deploy and manage service on aws, and azure.

FORMATION

Master professional en Data sciense & software developpment

ESEN - Manouba, Tunis | 2019 - 2021

Applied License in Business Informatics

ESEN - Manouba, Tunis | 2016 - 2019

Bachelor of Computer Science

High School of Bachir safar – Amdoun, Beja – Tunis | 2016

Intership

PixelJ - Ariana, Tunis | 2021

 Create price comparison engine on tunisia marketplaces using machine learning and integrate it into a website.

AMABusiness- Bardo, Tunis | 2019

• Intelligent transportation web application